<blog>
	<post>
		<date>April 23, 2022</date>
		<author>Anita Ramaswamy</author>
		<title>DJ and crypto startup founder 3LAU explains the value behind music NFTs</title>
		<imageURL>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/GettyImages-1384741375.jpg?w=604</imageURL>
		<summary>Crypto's music man 3LAU on how NFTs for music royalties can help artists and fans alike</summary>
		<body>When people think of NFTs, the first use case most of them likely think of is visual art. From Beeple's $69 million sale of a digital collage at Christie's to the Bored Apes Yacht Club collection, visual art has seemed to be most prominent use case for NFTs due to close similarities with traditional fine art investing. The fact that digital art can be viewed and replicated endlessly online has led to some confusion for plenty of consumers with what exactly they're buying, however.

'The idea that someone can just say, 'hey, this is mine now, I just saved the image to my laptop, and I'm using it as my background,' -it seems really obvious. But then when there's a real, true owner, and you can validate that on-chain, it makes that other person look kind of foolish, at least within the web3 community,' DJ and NFT art collector Justin Blau explained in an interview on the TechCrunch podcast Chain Reaction.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>April 23, 2022</date>
		<author>Brian Heater</author>
		<title>Alphabet-owned Intrinsic is acquiring fellow robotic software firm Vicarious</title>
		<imageURL>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Screen-Shot-2022-04-22-at-7.02.03-PM.jpg?w=748</imageURL>
		<summary>Alphabet X-birthed Intrinsic is acquiring fellow AI/robotic intelligence firm, Vicarious.</summary>
		<body>Alphabet X-birthed Intrinsic made its big debut last September. The subsidiary looks to buck its parent companys somewhat spotty robotics record with a software-first approach.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>April 23, 2022</date>
		<author>Christine Hall, Haje Jan Kamps</author>
		<title>Daily Crunch: Twitter to allow developers to build third-party apps</title>
		<imageURL>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/GettyImages-1055352580.jpg?w=601</imageURL>
		<summary>Hello friends and welcome to Daily Crunch, bringing you the most important startup, tech and venture capital news in a single package.</summary>
		<body>To get a roundup of TechCrunch's biggest and most important stories delivered to your inbox every day at 3 p.m. PT, subscribe here.

It's Earth Day, also known as April 22, 2022, and we are beyond grateful that the sun sets on another week.

We love our TechCrunch Live events, but we realize we don't always fit into everyone's calendars. Good news: They're now available as a podcast, too, so you can listen along at your leisure.

May your weekend be as energetic as you desire, and full of all the right types of surprises. Oh, and ice cream. - Christine and Haje</body>
	</post>
</blog>